

Henrik Mjaaland

Computer Engineer

18 November 1993



Gamleveien 14, 4315 Sandnes, Rogaland



+47 90215974



http://github.com/henmja



henrikmjaaland@hotmail.com

About Me ———

I am a computer engineer from Sandnes, Norway. I live in Lura with my fiancée. I have a bachelor degree in Computer Science, and I am currently working on a masters degree (also Computer Science). I have previously worked as a production operator, seller, gardener, and as a warehouse worker. Preesently, I am working as a control technician for Nærbø Kyllingslakt. There, the tasks are IT-related (f.ex. control the assembly lines). In my sparetime I like to run, lift, bike and play football. As a person I am outgoing, hard-working and honest.

Skills —

Python

Java

MATLAB

Go

Javascript

PHP

(*)[The skill scale is from 0 (Fundamental Awareness) to 6 (Expert).]

Education

since 2017 M.Sc. University of Stavanger

University of Stavanger

Computer Science B.Sc.

Computer Science

2009-2012 General Studies (Science) Sandnes VGS

Realfag

Portfolio

2014-2016

Github.com/Henmja

Website

https://www.henrikmjaaland.com

Certificates

2012	Driver's License, Class B
2012	Forklift License, T1
2016	Boating License

Experience

Current	Control Technician	Nærbø Kyllingslakt

2017-18 **Production Operator** Nortura Forus

2016 Gardener Facility Services

2015 Warehouse Worker Megaflis Forus

2013-14 Seller Burger Pizza Companiet

2012 Warehouse Worker REMA 1000 Distribusjon

References

References are given on demand.